Hey, do you have to fight with everyone?
Then why is he touching my things
?
Yes, your things will get worn out if he
plays.
Wait, I will complain about you to the teacher.
Yes, go and apply it.
No, vagina, you play.  This is crazy.  Bani,
he will come for a short while and then go away.
Yoni, come here and eat some bread.
No uncle, I don't want to eat it.
Why don't you want to eat? Come and sit here near me.
This is the condition of every child.  Just don't feed them bread.
Our girl is not ready to eat anything.
Go and prepare milk for it.
See that he doesn't drink and save him.
Oh yes, yes it is chocolate flavoured.  He will
drink it comfortably.  Yes, and it also contains calcium and
protein which will give him strength.
Hey, why are you making him drink from my box
?
Yes, so what will happen if he also drinks it?
Hey, have some shame, someone has come home and you are still fighting.
Hey mom, this girl's one comes separately for boys.
Yes, so will you refuse him now?   Let me do
one thing, I will place an order for the boy.
Get these Spiderman ones from Sipper Bull.
I won't let you drink it.
You are just going to beat me someday.   Okay, no problem, get it
delivered along with you.   Doesn't
water etc. leak into it?
No, I take this to school every day.
Okay, the order is placed, it is coming in 15 minutes.